* Shop
    
    Shop
    
    * Supplements
        
        Supplements

    * Health Benefit
        
        Health Benefit

* Learn
    
    Learn
    
    * Health Articles
        
        Health Articles

    * Health Benefit
        
        Health Benefit

    * Featured
        
        Featured

* Our Story
    
    Our Story

Country/region Afghanistan (USD $) Åland Islands (USD $) Albania (USD $) Andorra (USD $) Angola (USD $) Anguilla (USD $) Antigua & Barbuda (USD $) Argentina (USD $) Armenia (USD $) Aruba (USD $) Australia (USD $) Austria (USD $) Azerbaijan (USD $) Bahamas (USD $) Bahrain (USD $) Bangladesh (USD $) Barbados (USD $) Belarus (USD $) Belgium (USD $) Belize (USD $) Bermuda (USD $) Bhutan (USD $) Bolivia (USD $) Bosnia & Herzegovina (USD $) Brazil (USD $) British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $) British Virgin Islands (USD $) Brunei (USD $) Bulgaria (USD $) Burkina Faso (USD $) Burundi (USD $) Cameroon (USD $) Canada (USD $) Cape Verde (USD $) Caribbean Netherlands (USD $) Cayman Islands (USD $) Central African Republic (USD $) Chad (USD $) Chile (USD $) Christmas Island (USD $) Cocos (Keeling) Islands (USD $) Colombia (USD $) Comoros (USD $) Congo - Brazzaville (USD $) Congo - Kinshasa (USD $) Cook Islands (USD $) Costa Rica (USD $) Côte d’Ivoire (USD $) Croatia (USD $) Curaçao (USD $) Cyprus (USD $) Czechia (USD $) Denmark (USD $) Djibouti (USD $) Dominica (USD $) Dominican Republic (USD $) Ecuador (USD $) Egypt (USD $) El Salvador (USD $) Equatorial Guinea (USD $) Eritrea (USD $) Estonia (USD $) Eswatini (USD $) Ethiopia (USD $) Falkland Islands (USD $) Faroe Islands (USD $) Fiji (USD $) Finland (USD $) France (USD $) French Guiana (USD $) French Polynesia (USD $) French Southern Territories (USD $) Gabon (USD $) Gambia (USD $) Georgia (USD $) Germany (USD $) Ghana (USD $) Gibraltar (USD $) Greece (USD $) Greenland (USD $) Grenada (USD $) Guadeloupe (USD $) Guatemala (USD $) Guernsey (USD $) Guinea (USD $) Guinea-Bissau (USD $) Guyana (USD $) Haiti (USD $) Honduras (USD $) Hungary (USD $) Iceland (USD $) Indonesia (USD $) Iraq (USD $) Ireland (USD $) Isle of Man (USD $) Israel (USD $) Italy (USD $) Jamaica (USD $) Japan (USD $) Jersey (USD $) Jordan (USD $) Kazakhstan (USD $) Kenya (USD $) Kiribati (USD $) Kosovo (USD $) Kuwait (USD $) Kyrgyzstan (USD $) Laos (USD $) Latvia (USD $) Lebanon (USD $) Lesotho (USD $) Liberia (USD $) Libya (USD $) Liechtenstein (USD $) Lithuania (USD $) Luxembourg (USD $) Macao SAR (USD $) Madagascar (USD $) Malawi (USD $) Maldives (USD $) Mali (USD $) Malta (USD $) Martinique (USD $) Mauritania (USD $) Mauritius (USD $) Mayotte (USD $) Moldova (USD $) Monaco (USD $) Mongolia (USD $) Montenegro (USD $) Montserrat (USD $) Morocco (USD $) Mozambique (USD $) Myanmar (Burma) (USD $) Namibia (USD $) Nauru (USD $) Nepal (USD $) Netherlands (USD $) New Caledonia (USD $) Nicaragua (USD $) Niger (USD $) Nigeria (USD $) Niue (USD $) Norfolk Island (USD $) North Macedonia (USD $) Norway (USD $) Oman (USD $) Pakistan (USD $) Palestinian Territories (USD $) Panama (USD $) Papua New Guinea (USD $) Paraguay (USD $) Peru (USD $) Pitcairn Islands (USD $) Poland (USD $) Portugal (USD $) Qatar (USD $) Réunion (USD $) Romania (USD $) Russia (USD $) Rwanda (USD $) Samoa (USD $) San Marino (USD $) São Tomé & Príncipe (USD $) Saudi Arabia (USD $) Senegal (USD $) Serbia (USD $) Seychelles (USD $) Sierra Leone (USD $) Sint Maarten (USD $) Slovakia (USD $) Slovenia (USD $) Solomon Islands (USD $) Somalia (USD $) South Africa (USD $) South Georgia & South Sandwich Islands (USD $) South Korea (USD $) South Sudan (USD $) Sri Lanka (USD $) St. Barthélemy (USD $) St. Helena (USD $) St. Kitts & Nevis (USD $) St. Lucia (USD $) St. Martin (USD $) St. Pierre & Miquelon (USD $) St. Vincent & Grenadines (USD $) Sudan (USD $) Suriname (USD $) Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $) Sweden (USD $) Switzerland (USD $) Tajikistan (USD $) Tanzania (USD $) Timor-Leste (USD $) Togo (USD $) Tokelau (USD $) Tonga (USD $) Trinidad & Tobago (USD $) Tristan da Cunha (USD $) Tunisia (USD $) Türkiye (USD $) Turkmenistan (USD $) Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $) Tuvalu (USD $) U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $) Uganda (USD $) Ukraine (USD $) United Arab Emirates (USD $) United Kingdom (USD $) United States (USD $) Uruguay (USD $) Uzbekistan (USD $) Vanuatu (USD $) Vatican City (USD $) Venezuela (USD $) Wallis & Futuna (USD $) Western Sahara (USD $) Yemen (USD $) Zambia (USD $) Zimbabwe (USD $)

Update country/region

Country/region

USD $ | United Kingdom

* Shop
    
    * Supplements

    * Health Benefit

* Learn
    
    * Health Articles

    * Health Benefit

    * Featured

* Our Story

 Search [Search](#) [Log in](https://globalhealing.com/account/login) [Cart](https://globalhealing.com/cart)

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Continue shopping

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective date: June 29, 2021.

### General Disclaimer

Thank you for visiting Global Healing online and for reviewing our Privacy Policy. We strive to ensure that our customers and visitors are well-informed of the measures we have set in place to protect any personal information collected through our Website, as well as the storage and disposal of that information. Unless you reside in the EU, by exploring and using this Website, and by submitting information to us, you agree to our use of such information as described herein as well as the terms and conditions set forth in our Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices we utilize through the operation of [https://globalhealing.com](https://globalhealing.com/), and applies solely to information collected by this Website through such operation. Through this notice, you will be informed of the following:

1. What personal information is collected from your use of [https://globalhealing.com](https://globalhealing.com/), as well as how that information is used and with whom that information may be shared;
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of the information;
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information; and
4. How you may correct any potential inaccuracies in your information.

### Information, Collection, Use & Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this Website. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily provide to us via email, text messages or through other direct contact from you.

When you engage in a transaction on our Website, we may collect, directly from you, your name, email address, IP address, web browser, mailing address, shipping address, credit card information, phone number, age, and sex for the purpose of being able to perform the services provided through our Website. We are processing this information based upon your consent, our legitimate interests such as marketing and, with respect to the data necessary to process your payments, because it is necessary for the performance of your contract with us. Data will be transferred to countries outside of the EU so long as it is necessary for the purpose of carrying out our contractual obligations to you or you have granted us your consent. This information will only be retained for as long as it is necessary to carry out the purpose for which it is collected, to fulfill our contractual obligations, or as long as it is required by law. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active with us, but no longer than ten (10) years from the time that you cease having an active account. Of course, we will delete your personal data quickly upon request.

In order for us to be able to provide the services and goods available on our Website and to meet any of our related business obligations, you must provide the personal data that is required to do so. Without that data, we are not in a position to do so.

Websites such as Google and Facebook provide services we utilize to perform these valuable enhancement and improvement features, but the sharing of your information for the utilization of these services only extends to your basic contact information.

We may contact you via email in the future to inform you of special offers, new products or services, or changes to this Privacy Policy. However, should you not want to receive this special information, then you may choose not to by emailing us to inform us of your decision using the email provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Global Healing may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted third party partners. These partners may combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that Global Healing may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail. If you do not want Global Healing to collect information about you, please contact Global Healing to opt out.

The information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information may also be shared with other third-party marketers to bring you offers of interest. These third parties may share your information with others and may use this information for their own interest-based advertising and commercial purposes.

### Orders

To process an order for you, it is necessary for us to request some information from you through our order form, such as your name, shipping address, credit card number, and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. If, for some reason, we are having trouble processing your order, we will use this information to contact you and verify your order with you.

### Cookies

When you visit websites from your computer, the web servers utilized by those websites create small packets of information regarding your visit to the website. These small packets of information are known as “Cookies.” The websites you visit use these cookies to monitor your activity while visiting the website, such as which pages you visited and which links you accessed, and to record information about you. With this information, the websites can provide customized features to you in the event you return, thereby enhancing your experience with those websites.

There are two different types of cookies utilized by websites. The first is what is known as a “session” cookie. A session cookie temporarily records a small amount of information in your internet browser’s memory, but this information expires and is destroyed when you close your internet browser. The second type of cookie is known as a “persistent” cookie. Persistent cookies save the small amount of information created by your visit to a website to your computer’s hard drive and, in the event you revisit a website, your computer accesses the persistent cookie. Persistent cookies allow a website to understand what your interests were the last time you visited the website, and uses that information to enhance your experience with the website.

We use session and persistent cookies on our Website to enhance our users’ experience with [https://globalhealing.com](https://globalhealing.com/). By doing this, we are able to offer specific promotions or company information to you based on your previous orders and interests with Global Healing. For example, if you were interested in a specific product we offer, we could use your information from your visit to our Website to send you a special offer for that product or invite you to try a related product you may have been interested in but were unaware that we also offer. Our goal is that by using this information, we can optimize your experience with our Website by catering to your interests. We also want to use this information to help us make improvements to our Website where necessary. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser’s preferences by following its instructions. If you choose to disable cookies you may still browse our Website, but many of the features will not work.

We may also use these cookies to serve you relevant ads on Google. To opt-out of these ads, please see the information here: [https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en) and here: [https://steelhouse.com/opt-out/](https://steelhouse.com/opt-out/)

To opt-out of ad serving on Facebook, please see the information here: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

### Surveys & Contests

From time to time, our Website may request information from you in the form of surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you may choose whether or not to participate and disclose the requested information. The information requested by these surveys or contests may include your contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and your demographic information (such as your zip code and age level).

The contact information you provide through our contests will be used by us to notify winners and award prizes. The information you provide through our surveys will be used by us to monitor and improve the use and satisfaction of our Website, as previously discussed above.

Some of the surveys we utilize to monitor and enhance our Website and our customers’ experience with our Website are interactive surveys which ask you for certain personal information to join discussion forums, blogs, and other interactive Global Healing community features such as signing up to receive email notifications or newsletters. When you participate in one of these activities, the information that you provide may be visible to other web users of [https://globalhealing.com](https://globalhealing.com/). Any information you provide will be protected to the extent permissible under the Freedom of Information Act and Privacy Act.

### Text Messaging

This Messaging Program Privacy Policy explains how Global Healing collects and uses information about you in relation to its text message marketing program (the “Messaging Service”). We use Exponea and Attentive to provide the Messaging Service to you. For the purposes of the Messaging Service, Exponea or Attentive acts as our service provider and data processor of your information.

We collect information about you, including information you directly provide when you use the Messaging Service. For example, we collect the phone number and/or email address you provided when signing up for the Messaging Service. When you send messages via the Messaging Service, we will also collect your messaging history and any information included in those messages.  
We may also collect information about you using cookies or similar technologies. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your device. Cookies enable personalization of your experience on the Messaging Service. For example, we use cookies to track the items in your Shopping Cart and may use that information to send you triggered text campaigns (e.g., sending you personalized text messages such as shopping cart reminders).

We use your information to deliver, analyze, maintain and support the Messaging Service. We may also use your information to enhance the Messaging Service features and customize and personalize your experiences on the Messaging Service.

Consent to receive automated marketing text messages is not a condition of any purchase. You can opt-out of receiving further commercial text messages via the Messaging Service by responding to any of our text messages with any of the following replies: STOP, END, CANCEL, UNSUBSCRIBE, or QUIT.

Mobile discount codes comprise of alphanumeric characters that begin with 'Mobile'. To work correctly, please ensure you enter the full discount code.

### Data Processors

We do not own or control any servers or databases. As a result, personal data is only stored on third-party servers, which act as data processors. The personal data that we collect is stored on Amazon Web Services (AWS) in the US and is kept for 120 months. Amazon, DoubleClick for Publishers and Microsoft Ads collect cookies and usage data for advertising purposes. Google Analytics, Facebook Ads conversion tracking, AddThis, FourSixty, Google Ads conversion tracking, Klevu, Claritas, Glew, Hotjar Form Analysis & Conversion Funnels, and analytics that are directly collected by us collect cookies and usage data for analytics purposes. Google Customer Reviews collects your email address, transaction number, products purchased, and name for analytics purposes. Impact collects your order number, transaction number, and products purchased for affiliate marketing purposes. YouTube Video Widget collect cookies and usage data for the purpose of displaying content from external platforms. Shopify Payments and OrderGroove collect personal data as specified in their privacy policy for the purpose of handling payments. Kount also collects personal data to detect fraud. Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings collects cookies, usage data, and other personal data as may be specified in their privacy policy for heat mapping and session recording purposes. Hotjar Recruit User Testers collects cookies, usage data, and various types of other data for the purpose of interacting with data collection platforms and other third parties. Facebook like button and social widgets, TikTok, Twitter, AddThis and Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets collect cookies and usage data for the purpose of interacting with external social networks and platforms. Salesforce collects your email and contact information for customer relationship management. Hotjar Poll & Survey widgets collect cookies, usage data, and other types of data for the purpose of interacting with online survey platforms. Typeform, ViralSweep and Outgrow collects your email address and products purchased for the purpose of interacting with online survey platforms. Shopify, Exponea, Zapier collect your email address and name for the purpose of managing contacts and sending messages. Exponea and Nosto collects your email address, name, address, mobile, home and work numbers, order information, product interests, content topic interests, loyalty information, customer number, IP address, operating system, location information, and other device information for the purpose of managing contacts and sending messages. Yotpo collect your email address, order number, and name for the purpose of managing contacts and sending messages. ShipStation, UPS, Endicia, United States Postal Service, and FedEx collect your name, phone number, email address, shipping information, order number, and products purchased for shipping purposes. Zendesk collects your email address, name, phone number, and other types of data as specified in their privacy policy for the purpose of managing support and contact requests. SteelHouse, Liveclicker, Facebook Remarketing, and Remarketing through Google Analytics for Display collect cookies and usage data for remarketing and behavioral targeting purposes. Facebook Custom Audience collects cookies and usage data for the purpose of behavioral targeting. Avalara collects your shipping information, order number and products purchased for tax purposes. Dropbox stores backups of this information for tax purposes. GeoIP collects your IP to share important messaging. Google Tag Manager collects cookies and usage data for the purpose of distributing it to tracking platforms.

### Termination of Consent

You have the right, at any time, to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data. The withdrawal of your consent will not affect or invalidate the lawfulness of any data processing based upon your original consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of that consent.

### Correction, Amendment, or Deletion of Information

You have the right to have your personal data corrected, erased, and to terminate the further dissemination of your personal data with third parties, or to have third parties cease processing your personal data. In the event that you desire to revoke your previously granted consent to our Website collecting any personal data, and/or wish to have such information corrected, amended or deleted, and/or terminate the further dissemination of your personal data or to have third parties cease processing your personal data, you can do so by contacting Saul Torres, Global Healing, 1242 N Post Oak, Suite 100, Houston, TX 77055, (800) 476-0016 Ext. 223, [\[email protected\]](https://globalhealing.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by clicking [here](https://globalhealing.com/pages/privacy-request).

If you wish to opt-out of sharing your information with third parties, you can do so by clicking [here](https://globalhealing.com/pages/privacy-request).

CCPA — California Residents

CCPA is known as the California Consumer Privacy Act. As a California resident, you have the right to access your personal information, know what personal information is collected about you, opt-out of the collection of your personal information, know whether your personal information is sold or disclosed to any third party company/organization, and delete your information within 45 days of your request.

### Right to Your Personal Data

You are entitled to receive a copy of your personal data free of charge so long as your request is not manifestly unfounded or excessive. We must provide the requested information within one month of our receipt of your request, which time period can be extended by two additional months if necessary, so long as we inform you of the extension within one month of receiving your request and of the reasons for the delay. In order to submit an access request, please contact Saul Torres, Global Healing, 1242 N Post Oak, Suite 100, Houston, TX 77055, (800) 476-0016 Ext. 223, [\[email protected\]](https://globalhealing.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by clicking [here](https://globalhealing.com/pages/privacy-request).

### Right to Object to Profiling & Direct Marketing

To the extent that we may collect your personal data for the purposes of conducting profiling or direct marketing, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data for those purposes. In the event that you object to processing for those purposes, we will no longer process your personal data for those purposes.

### Data Portability

You have the right to receive your personal data in a commonly used and machine-readable format and to have your personal data transmitted to another information technology environment if it is technically feasible to do so.

### Notification of Data Breach

In the event of a data breach that is likely to result in a risk to your rights and freedom, within 72 hours of our becoming aware of the breach, we are required to report it to you and the appropriate authorities. We are not required to notify you of such a breach if we have implemented appropriate security measures intended to render your personal data unintelligible to an unauthorized person, have taken subsequent measures to ensure that any high risk to you does not occur, or if it would involve a disproportionate effort on our behalf, in which event a public communication will suffice.

### Complaints

You have the right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority (Data Protection Authority) of a member state of the EU that is your habitual residence, your place of work, or the place of the alleged infringement of your rights.

### Information Disposal

In order to protect your personal information, we maintain and destroy all electronically submitted information according to the principles of the Federal Records Act and the regulations and records schedules of the National Archives and Records Administration. It is also possible that some of the information you provide to us through our Website may be subject to the Privacy Act and the Freedom of Information Act. You can review your rights regarding your information by visiting the Freedom of Information Act homepage at [www.gsa.gov/portal/content/104389](https://www.gsa.gov/reference/freedom-of-information-act-foia).

### Children’s Personal Data

Although Global Healing does not specifically market to children under the age of thirteen (13), we care and are concerned with the privacy of child web users. Thus, Global Healing intends on fully complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and all provisions and regulations prescribed by COPPA, as well as California’s Online Eraser Law, and the Delaware Online Privacy and Protection Act (“DOPPA”).

Global Healing does not knowingly contact, solicit, record, or collect personal information from children under the age of 13 in the U.S., under the age of 18 in California and Delaware, and under the age of 16 in the EU and, in the event we discover that we have been defrauded or deceived into collecting such information, we will either immediately use that information to obtain parental consent or completely destroy the information collected.

Parents have the right to review the personal data that we may have collected about their children. Parents can, at any time, refuse to permit us to collect any more personal data about their children, and can request that we delete from our records all of the personal data that we have collected about their children. Parents should keep in mind that a request to delete such information about their children means that their children will not be able to utilize our Website. In order to request access to, change, or delete their child’s personal data, parents can send an email to us at [\[email protected\]](https://globalhealing.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). It will be necessary for you to authenticate yourself as the child’s parent to receive any information about that child. A valid request to delete personal data will be undertaken within a reasonable period of time.

Minors under the age of 18 residing in California and Delaware may remove, or may request the removal of, any information that they have published on our Website. This can be accomplished by contacting Saul Torres, Global Healing, 1242 N Post Oak, Suite 100, Houston, TX 77055, (800) 476-0016 Ext. 223, [\[email protected\]](https://globalhealing.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by clicking [here](https://globalhealing.com/pages/privacy-request). Any removal of posted information does not ensure the complete or comprehensive removal of the information published on our Website.

### Social Medial & Third-Party Websites

We utilize various social media platforms and websites to interact with our customers, improve our customers’ experience with our Website, promote our products and community, educate our customers and the public regarding our products, and engage with potential customers. While our Website may have links to other websites, we do not use these platforms or other third- party websites to record, solicit, or collect personal information from our customers or web visitors. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such sites. They may also use cookies and other technologies. However, we do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies that they may use. As such, the information practices of these sites are not covered by our Privacy Policy, but rather are covered by their respective privacy policies. Thus, please be aware of when you are leaving this Website and take the time to review the privacy policies of any such third-party websites, especially if they are in the habit of collecting your personal data.

The privacy policies of the social media platforms and websites we utilize to grow the Global Healing community are listed below and may be accessed by clicking on the included hyperlink.

Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

YouTube: [https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy\_guidelines](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines)

Pinterest: [https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)

Instagram: [https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/](https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/)

### General Security & Options

We take your personal information quite seriously and understand that you do too. Thus, you may choose to decline any future contact from us at any time.

We also take several precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive personal information to us through [https://globalhealing.com](https://globalhealing.com/), your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect this information (such as your credit card data), we encrypt and securely transmit this information to our servers. You can verify our secure methods by looking for a closed-lock icon at the bottom of your internet browser or for looking for “https” at the beginning of the website at the top of your internet browser. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee the complete security of your information inasmuch as no security systems are foolproof. It is also important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your information as well as to your computer.

While we utilize encryption to protect the information you submit online, we also take serious steps to ensure the protection of your information offline. Only Global Healing employees who are required to access your information to perform a specific job (such as billing a customer or providing customer service) are granted access to your personal information. Even further, the computers and servers where we store your information are kept in secure locations and environments.

### Notice

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Unless you reside in the EU, all material changes to this Privacy Policy are effective immediately upon its posting on this section of our Website. If you reside in the EU, you will have to provide your consent to any such changes. We may also post these changes in the Terms of Use section of this Website and/or by sending an email to users who have provided us with their email address for this notification purpose.

We hope you enjoy your visit to [https://globalhealing.com](https://globalhealing.com/), and we appreciate your support and involvement in the Global Healing community!

Your journey to health starts here.

 Sign Up

 I agree to receive marketing emails. [View Privacy Policy](https://globalhealing.com/pages/privacy-policy).

Success! You'll be receiving an email shortly.

My Account

Customer Care

Our Story

Our Company

Country/region
--------------

Afghanistan (USD $) Åland Islands (USD $) Albania (USD $) Andorra (USD $) Angola (USD $) Anguilla (USD $) Antigua & Barbuda (USD $) Argentina (USD $) Armenia (USD $) Aruba (USD $) Australia (USD $) Austria (USD $) Azerbaijan (USD $) Bahamas (USD $) Bahrain (USD $) Bangladesh (USD $) Barbados (USD $) Belarus (USD $) Belgium (USD $) Belize (USD $) Bermuda (USD $) Bhutan (USD $) Bolivia (USD $) Bosnia & Herzegovina (USD $) Brazil (USD $) British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $) British Virgin Islands (USD $) Brunei (USD $) Bulgaria (USD $) Burkina Faso (USD $) Burundi (USD $) Cameroon (USD $) Canada (USD $) Cape Verde (USD $) Caribbean Netherlands (USD $) Cayman Islands (USD $) Central African Republic (USD $) Chad (USD $) Chile (USD $) Christmas Island (USD $) Cocos (Keeling) Islands (USD $) Colombia (USD $) Comoros (USD $) Congo - Brazzaville (USD $) Congo - Kinshasa (USD $) Cook Islands (USD $) Costa Rica (USD $) Côte d’Ivoire (USD $) Croatia (USD $) Curaçao (USD $) Cyprus (USD $) Czechia (USD $) Denmark (USD $) Djibouti (USD $) Dominica (USD $) Dominican Republic (USD $) Ecuador (USD $) Egypt (USD $) El Salvador (USD $) Equatorial Guinea (USD $) Eritrea (USD $) Estonia (USD $) Eswatini (USD $) Ethiopia (USD $) Falkland Islands (USD $) Faroe Islands (USD $) Fiji (USD $) Finland (USD $) France (USD $) French Guiana (USD $) French Polynesia (USD $) French Southern Territories (USD $) Gabon (USD $) Gambia (USD $) Georgia (USD $) Germany (USD $) Ghana (USD $) Gibraltar (USD $) Greece (USD $) Greenland (USD $) Grenada (USD $) Guadeloupe (USD $) Guatemala (USD $) Guernsey (USD $) Guinea (USD $) Guinea-Bissau (USD $) Guyana (USD $) Haiti (USD $) Honduras (USD $) Hungary (USD $) Iceland (USD $) Indonesia (USD $) Iraq (USD $) Ireland (USD $) Isle of Man (USD $) Israel (USD $) Italy (USD $) Jamaica (USD $) Japan (USD $) Jersey (USD $) Jordan (USD $) Kazakhstan (USD $) Kenya (USD $) Kiribati (USD $) Kosovo (USD $) Kuwait (USD $) Kyrgyzstan (USD $) Laos (USD $) Latvia (USD $) Lebanon (USD $) Lesotho (USD $) Liberia (USD $) Libya (USD $) Liechtenstein (USD $) Lithuania (USD $) Luxembourg (USD $) Macao SAR (USD $) Madagascar (USD $) Malawi (USD $) Maldives (USD $) Mali (USD $) Malta (USD $) Martinique (USD $) Mauritania (USD $) Mauritius (USD $) Mayotte (USD $) Moldova (USD $) Monaco (USD $) Mongolia (USD $) Montenegro (USD $) Montserrat (USD $) Morocco (USD $) Mozambique (USD $) Myanmar (Burma) (USD $) Namibia (USD $) Nauru (USD $) Nepal (USD $) Netherlands (USD $) New Caledonia (USD $) Nicaragua (USD $) Niger (USD $) Nigeria (USD $) Niue (USD $) Norfolk Island (USD $) North Macedonia (USD $) Norway (USD $) Oman (USD $) Pakistan (USD $) Palestinian Territories (USD $) Panama (USD $) Papua New Guinea (USD $) Paraguay (USD $) Peru (USD $) Pitcairn Islands (USD $) Poland (USD $) Portugal (USD $) Qatar (USD $) Réunion (USD $) Romania (USD $) Russia (USD $) Rwanda (USD $) Samoa (USD $) San Marino (USD $) São Tomé & Príncipe (USD $) Saudi Arabia (USD $) Senegal (USD $) Serbia (USD $) Seychelles (USD $) Sierra Leone (USD $) Sint Maarten (USD $) Slovakia (USD $) Slovenia (USD $) Solomon Islands (USD $) Somalia (USD $) South Africa (USD $) South Georgia & South Sandwich Islands (USD $) South Korea (USD $) South Sudan (USD $) Sri Lanka (USD $) St. Barthélemy (USD $) St. Helena (USD $) St. Kitts & Nevis (USD $) St. Lucia (USD $) St. Martin (USD $) St. Pierre & Miquelon (USD $) St. Vincent & Grenadines (USD $) Sudan (USD $) Suriname (USD $) Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $) Sweden (USD $) Switzerland (USD $) Tajikistan (USD $) Tanzania (USD $) Timor-Leste (USD $) Togo (USD $) Tokelau (USD $) Tonga (USD $) Trinidad & Tobago (USD $) Tristan da Cunha (USD $) Tunisia (USD $) Türkiye (USD $) Turkmenistan (USD $) Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $) Tuvalu (USD $) U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $) Uganda (USD $) Ukraine (USD $) United Arab Emirates (USD $) United Kingdom (USD $) United States (USD $) Uruguay (USD $) Uzbekistan (USD $) Vanuatu (USD $) Vatican City (USD $) Venezuela (USD $) Wallis & Futuna (USD $) Western Sahara (USD $) Yemen (USD $) Zambia (USD $) Zimbabwe (USD $)

Update country/region

Country/region
--------------

USD $ | United Kingdom

© 2024, [Global Healing](https://globalhealing.com/) [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

Have a question? We'd love to help!  
  
[1242 N Post Oak Rd Suite 100,  
Houston, TX 77055](https://g.page/global-healing-houston)  

All testimonials and product reviews are authentic from actual customers. Documentation is available for legal inspection. Product reviews are within range of typicality.  
Information and statements made are for education purposes and are not intended to replace the advice of your treating doctor. Global Healing does not dispense medical advice, prescribe, or diagnose illness. The views and nutritional advice expressed by Global Healing are not intended to be a substitute for conventional medical service. If you have a severe medical condition or health concern, see your physician. This Web site contains links to Web sites operated by other parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We are not responsible for the content or products of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. Global Healing does not adopt any medical claims which may have been made in 3rd party references. Where Global Healing has control over the posting or other communications of such claims to the public, Global Healing will make its best effort to remove such claims.

These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
